你 你还醒着吗
Are -- Are you awake?
我大概两小时前睡了6分钟
I slept for six minutes two hours ago.
我得去服一片安眠药
I'm gonna have to take a sleeping pill,
这意味着你得负责藏好我的车钥匙
which means you're gonna have to hide my car keys,
电脑和乡村女歌手芮芭·麦克伊泰假发
laptop, and Reba McEntire wig.
最近几天快把人折磨疯了
It's been a crazy couple days.
昨天我发现我没得到
Uh, yesterday, I found out I didn't get
我努力追求的大学橄榄球教练工作
the college football coaching job that I had been chasing.
我 我伤心欲绝
I was -- I was devastated.
就在那之前片刻
And moments before that,
我们收到曾经的领养机构打来的电话
we got a phone call from our old adoption agency
说我们有领养一个男孩的机会
with the opportunity for us to adopt a baby boy.
上帝关上一扇门
So, a door closes...
就会给你打开一扇窗 但是 你该去应窗吗
A window opens. But do you answer it?
没有"应窗"这个说法
You don't answer windows.
你一定开心死了吧 小卡说错话了呢
Well, how fun for you. Cam made a little mistake.
我不断在脑海里列举这事的各种利弊
I keep making lists of all the pros and cons in my head.
婴儿身上的气味既算利也算弊
Uh, the -- the way a baby smells is on both.
好吧 说说利项 开始
Okay, alright. Pros, go.
好的 有个孩子让我们爱 孩子咯咯笑的声音
Okay, well, a baby to love. The sound of giggling.
一个更大的家庭
You know, a bigger family,
等我们老了 就多个人来决定要不要拔管
an extra vote on whether to pull the plug on us when we get old.
我担心莉莉个性一触即发 手抖就拔
I'm worried that Lily has an itchy trigger finger.
是啊 再养个孩子就能帮我们搞清楚
Yeah, and another child would help us figure out
莉莉的性格有多少是我们的问题
how much of Lily's personality is our fault
有多少是她自身的问题
and what's on her.
能沉冤昭雪真的挺好的
It would be nice to be vindicated.
再想想别的利项 圣诞节
Okay, other pros -- Christmases.
将孩子的小脚趾第一次伸进海水里
Dipping little toes into the ocean for the first time,
以及小宝宝穿着睡衣跑向门
the way a toddler run towards the door
嘴里喊着"爹地"的小萌样儿
in their jammies saying, "Daddy!"
你快说几个弊项敲醒我
Okay, you'd better hit me with some cons.
我简直快要排卵了
I'm practically ovulating.
好吧 没有觉睡 车座要改 换尿布
Okay, no sleep, car seats, diapers,
感冒咳嗽什么的 经常要去看医生
coughs and colds, all -- all the doctor's appointments,
-塑料玩具扔得到处都是 -到处都是
- plastic toys everywhere. - Everywhere.
我们家本来就已经太小了
Our -- Our place is already too small.
我们的卧室不够
We don't have enough bedrooms.
天啊 时间紧迫
Oh, God, the clock is ticking.
我们只有半天时间就要给出答复了
We have half a day to give them an answer.
好了 别胡思乱想了
Okay, you know what, no thinking.
数到三 一起说要还是不要
On the count of three, say yes or no.
一 二 三
One, two, three...
-我不知道 -我决定不了
- I don't know. - I can't decide!
外面怎么有辆雪佛兰车 还有个司机在等着
Why is there a black Suburban outside with a driver?
是我们公司派来的
My company sent it.
我要负责"希洛动力"
I'm manning the Helo Dynamics booth
在加州理工学院的招聘会
for the job recruitment fair at Caltech.
瞧瞧你 有巨型SUV和专职司机接驾呢
Look at you, being chauffeured in a giant SUV.
我想象你开车的样子 是坐在丰田普锐斯车里哭
When I picture you driving, you're crying in a Prius.
别人给我开车 我的确哭得少些
I do cry less when I'm driven.
你这身衣服也太正点了吧
And that outfit is on point.
毕竟这对我来说是衣锦还乡 凯旋而归
Well, I mean, it's -- it's sort of a triumphant return for me.
我在那个大学辛辛苦苦念了四年 头发冒油懒得管
I spent four years there in sweats, with greasy hair,
一心只在乎成绩
caring only about grades.
大家唯一一次注意到我
The only time anyone ever noticed me
是我在期末考试周期间 焦虑到把眉毛都拔光了
was when I pulled out all my eyebrows during finals week.
现在我有份好工作 住着奢华的公寓
Now I have a big job, swanky apartment,
一双鞋的价钱比我第一个笔记本电脑还要贵
shoes that cost more than my first laptop...
简直就像是部浪漫喜剧
Oh, it's like a rom-com --
你离开时是个书呆子 归来时成了性感书呆子
you left a nerd and returned a hot nerd.
说到性感的人
Speaking of hot people,
或许我也应该去为我们诺普公司招些人
maybe I should go and recruit for NERP.
出于法律原因
For legal reasons,
我们需要科学方面的人才来为产品背书
we need a science-y person to endorse product.
毕竟我们这群大学没毕业的人
Considering we're all a bunch of people who didn't graduate college,
卖的很多产品可是广被你们内服外用呢
we sell a lot of products that go inside of you.
得了吧 不是这么个操作法
Yeah, no, it doesn't really work that way.
首先 你必须获得邀请
A, you have to be invited,
其次 稍微自重点的科学家
and B, no self-respecting scientist
都不可能为你们公司售卖的智商税产品站台
is going to endorse the nonsense your company is pushing.
瞎说什么呢 我们出品的含铜牙膏
Excuse me, but our copper-infused toothpaste
位列食品药品管理局的重点"监督"产品前十呢
is on the FDA's top ten items to watch, so...
菲尔 你能过来一下吗
Phil! Phil, can you come in here?
我为视频面试准备了一小段演讲展示
I've worked up a little presentation for my Skype interview,
我希望听听你的意见反馈
and I would love to get your feedback.
好啊 来吧
Yes, please!
我的魔术表演你一直都很捧场
You've been such a cheerleader for me with all my magic shows
包括南加房宴 我也很乐意支持你
and SCARB dinners, I'd love to be yours.
来吧
Hit it.
我必须这就打住你
I'm gonna stop you right there.
我已经好几个月没工作了
I've been out of work for a few months,
我变得有点惴惴不安
and I've gotten kinda antsy.
为排遣焦虑 我试过打扫卫生 整理物品
To channel my anxiety, I have cleaned, I have organized.
或许有点强迫症的程度
Perhaps a bit obsessively.
甚至去看了医生
Doctors were consulted.
就一个 心理治疗师而已 甚至不是真正的医生
One -- a therapist, so not even a real doctor.
但很快就停药了
But meds were quickly dismissed.
我们不想要性欲方面的副作用
We didn't want the sexual side effects.
总之呢
Anyway...
我打算将我的焦虑转变成事业
I am going to channel my anxiety into a career.
我即将面试我的梦想工作
I am interviewing for my dream job --
我最爱的整理连锁店"收纳良品"的高级副总裁
Senior VP of my favorite organizing chain store, organize 'Em!
我太激动了 我可能会拥有一份整理...
I'm so excited, I could have an organaz--
你不至于堕落到这地步
You're better than that.
所以在整个面试过程中
So, throughout the call,
我会一直提到这个整理系统
I'm gonna be referring to this organizational system
-聪明 -是啊 瞧好了
- Smart. - Yeah. Watch.
贝克曼女士 这观点可真有趣
Oh, Ms. Beckman, what an interesting point.
我应该记下来
I should jot that down.
那是什么鬼声音
What the hell is that?
天啊 什么
Oh, my God. What?
对了 我忘了告诉你你爸过来给我帮忙
Oh, yeah, I forgot to tell you, your dad came over to help me.
我打算把楼梯修好
I gotta fix that step.
它裂开了
It splintered.
我早上没踩稳 结果就脑袋着地了
I wiped out this morning and landed on my head.
好吧 但我得面试啊
Yeah, but my call.
我们必须赶紧修好 否则有人会受伤的
We gotta take care of that before someone gets hurt.
已经有人受伤了
Someone did.
万一是海莉抱着孩子摔了怎么办 或者迪兰
I mean, what if it was Haley with the babies? Or Dylan?
-或者... -或者我 我都摔吐了
- Or...? - Or me. I threw up.
我的天 昨天歌洛莉亚还是穿着高跟鞋来的
Holy Moses. Gloria was here yesterday in heels.
她也可能会摔得很惨的
That could've been ugly.
我昏昏欲睡
I'm sleepy.
小子 你得挪开 不然你会把别人绊倒的
Buddy, you gotta move. Someone's gonna trip over you.
各位 你们不能现在干这事 明白吗
Hey, guys, we can't do this right now, okay?
我1:23时有个面试
I've got -- I've got an interview at 1:23.
这时间定得好具体
Well, that's specific.
不 对奥黛丽·贝克曼来说不算什么
No, not for Audrey Beckman.
她的整个人生 安排都精确到秒
Her whole life is scheduled down to the second.
她简直是强迫症人群的神
She's a god to OCD people.
不然你以为我什么要买那个保险杠贴纸
Why do you think I've got that bumper sticker
上面写着"像贝克曼一样井井有条"
that says "Straighten It Like Beckman"?
我现在能下来了吗
Can I come down now?
如果宝宝们醒来时 我没准备好奶瓶
If I don't have the babies' bottles when they wake up,
他们就会发脾气
they're mean.
你还没遇到"可怕的两岁期"呢
You're not even in the terrible twos yet.
那是什么时候开始啊
Oh, when do those start?
好了 就快到时间点了
Okay, look, it's almost time.
拜托 别弄出任何噪音
Just please, nobody make any noise,
任何人都不准进那间办公室
nobody go in that office.
我现在做好了完全的准备
I have all my ducks in a row.
我先上楼换个衣服就好
I'm just gonna run upstairs and change my shirt.
好吧 但是小心点
Oh, okay, but be careful.
我知道自己在干什么 我没问题的
I know what I'm doing, I have got this.
要命了 老天爷啊
Oh, boy! Oh, God!
我的腿卡在里面了
My leg is stuck!
谁快想想办法啊
Somebody do something!
我很擅长取下卡住的戒指
I'm really good at getting rings off.
你想让我给你大腿涂黄油做润滑吗
Do you want me to butter your thighs?
迪伦 有时我喜欢把话先在心里过一遍
Hey, Dylan, sometimes I like to play things out
看没有歧义再说出口
in my head first, if that's helpful.
亲爱的 我们想和你说个事
Hey, honey, uh, we need to talk to you about something.
宝贝 这是件大事
Sweetie, this is something pretty big,
我希望你做好心理准备
and I -- I want you to brace yourself.
领养机构联系了我们...
The adoption agency called --
我死也不回去
I'm not going back!
你知道软弱有特权的孩子在岘港会有什么下场吗
Do you know what happens to soft, entitled kids in Da Nang?
不不不 不是的
No, no, no, no, no, no! No, no.
不是的
N-No. No.
有一个男婴...
There's a baby boy --
我觉得你们应该收养他
I think you should do it.
-真的吗 你这么轻易就同意了 -什么
- Really? Just -- Just like that? - What?
只要我去朋友家过夜时能让你们不再来看 什么都行
Whatever stops you dropping by my sleepovers.
你们对我过度关注了
You guys are way too focused on me.
再说 有个弟弟会很欢乐的
Plus, I think it'd be fun to have a baby brother.
虽然...
Although...
虽然什么
Although what?
你们现在养娃不会太老了吗
Aren't you guys kind of old to be having a baby?
我马上要进入夜夜笙歌的青少年时期
I'm getting into the juicy part of my teen years.
万一你们死了 我可不想接手带娃
I don't want to have to take over for you.
我们也没那么老好吗
Okay, we are not that old.
你们都50高寿了
You're like 50.
什么鬼 当然没有
Oh, my God! No!
小爸才44岁 我48岁
Daddy's 44, and I'm 48.
你们知道等宝宝上高三时
You do realize when the baby's a senior in high school,
你们就是拿养老金的长者了吧
you guys will be senior citizens?
我们才不是长...
We will not be senior c--
-小卡 -66
- Cam. - Sixty-six.
到时我66岁
I'll be sixty-six.
我就是61岁
And I'll be sixty-one.
是62啦
Well, sixty-two.
没到六月生日不算啦
Not until June!
没用啊 我的腿还紧紧卡在里面
It's not working! My leg is really stuck in there!
也许该再考虑下我的提议了
It might be time to return to my idea.
我绝不会砍掉我的腿
I'm not cutting my leg off.
想想装上一条机械腿后 你会跑得多快啊
Think about how fast you would run with a robot leg.
卢克 你妈妈怎么可能装一条机械腿
Luke, your mom's not getting a robot leg!
她应该装两条 不然她跑起来只会绕圈
She'd need two, or she'd just run in circles.
好了 我们该看看楼梯下面
Come on, let's check under the stairs.
没错 拜托了 快点
Yes, please, and hurry!
这房子怎么回事
What the hell's the matter with this house?
怎么会坏掉两级楼梯
How could two steps be broken?
天啊 湿气好重 我头发都要变卷了
My God, the humidity. My hair's gonna frizz out.
所以我从来不给别人看我在越南的照片
That's why I never show any pictures from 'Nam.
糟了 我把给菇木装的加湿器
Oh, no, I totally forgot about the humidifier
忘得一干二净了
for my mushroom log.
它需要阴暗和潮湿环境
It needed darkness and moisture.
一定是腐蚀了木头
It must have rotted the wood.
老婆 你真的卡得死死的
Wow, honey, you're really wedged in here tight.
是啊 没在开玩笑的
Yeah, no kidding.
你为什么不能像个正常人一样
Why can't you buy your mushrooms at a store,
直接从商店买蘑菇
like a normal person?
店里买的蘑菇
Store-bought mushrooms?
你这婴儿潮一代和我这代之间真的有代沟
You really don't get my generation, Boomer.
也许这样能让你顿悟
Maybe this'll enlighten you.
张嘴
Open up.
把你的脏手拿开
Get your hand away from my --
张嘴啦
Open up!
真特么好吃
That's damn good.
我为什么总是拒绝尝试新事物
Why do I always default to "No"?
歌洛莉亚是对的吗 我该尝试修身牛仔裤吗
Is Gloria right? Should I try slim-cut jeans?
下面是怎么回事啊
Guys! What's going on down there?!
你的脚卡在两条水管之间
Your foot's stuck between two copper pipes.
我们得把水管锯开
We're gonna have to cut it.
可能需要一些时间
It might take a while.
我等不了
I don't have a while!
真不敢相信 我要错过面试了
I can't believe this. I'm going to miss my interview.
这可是我的梦想工作啊
And this was my dream job!
我本来能收纳好整个世界
I was gonna get to organize the whole world.
现在一切都只能保持混乱的原状
And now everything is gonna stay so messy.
你不能重新约个时间吗
Can't you just reschedule it?
不行 菲尔 那我会像个不靠谱的鸽王
No! Phil, I'd look like a flake!
这可是收纳公司
This is an organizational company,
不像你们房产界那么懒散随意
not the loosey-goosey world of real estate,
你们都只会说"中午十二点到三点见
where everything's "See you noon to three,
我会带曲奇来"
and I'll bring the cookies"!
抱歉 我拿你撒气了
Sorry. I'm lashing out.
没关系 狮子不会因为绵羊的看法
No, it's okay. The lion doesn't lose sleep
而辗转失眠
over the opinions of sheep.
宝贝 你就在那里接电话呗
Honey, just take the call from there.
我在楼梯上接电话看起来会多荒唐啊
How ridiculous would I look taking a call on stairs?
再说 我需要那些架子 因为我已经精心
Plus, I need my shelves, 'cause I had this whole thing
摆好了各种产品还有...
worked out with the products and --
你不需要搞这些噱头
You don't need gimmicks!
你曾是普利契特衣柜的牛逼CEO
You were the C.E.O. for Pritchett's freakin' Closets.
你知道有多少人能说这句话吗
You know how many people can say that?
只有我和你
Me and you!
还有玛格丽特 我每五年
And Margaret every five years,
去做结肠镜检查时 都交给她代班
when I went under for my colonoscopy.
好吧 把电话给我
Fine. Give me my phone.
我就在这里搞砸我的面试
I'll bomb the interview from right here.
她失去自信了 她需要那些架子
She's lost her confidence. She needs those shelves.
其实 如果她去不了办公室
You know what, if she can't get to the office,
我们可以把办公室搬到她旁边
we can bring the office to her.
你在盯着看
You're staring.
我头发炸毛了 对不对
I'm frizzing, aren't I?
我必须承认 走进那校园
I've got to admit, walking onto that campus...
那么多人注视着我 崇拜我
All those eyes on me, the adoration...
感觉很好 感觉这是对的
It felt good. It felt right.
感觉我得到的这些待遇都是应得的
Like I had earned everything that was coming my way.
你烂透了
You suck!
不 就是你
No! You!
什么
What?
希洛动力超邪恶
Helo Dynamics is evil!
你说什么 我们帮助别人
Excuse me? We help people.
是啊 帮那些法西斯分子 独裁者 寡头
Yeah! People like fascists, dictators, oligarchs.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我们不过是制造能检测
We make things like facial scanners
遗传病倾向的面部扫描仪
that detect predisposition to genetic diseases.
残暴政府就用这个来
Which oppressive governments use
识别持不同政见者
to identify political dissidents.
但这也能用在视频聊天里
Well, I mean, it's also used on video chats
把你自己变成独角兽啊
to turn yourself into a unicorn.
还有比这更好玩的吗
Name one thing more fun!
穿着你的名牌高跟鞋滚出去 见钱眼开的垃圾
Why don't you walk your fancy shoes outta here, you sellout?!
为什么有个穿凉鞋还配袜子的土逼
Why is someone wearing socks and sandals
在辱骂你绝美的高跟鞋
yelling at your fabulous shoes?
-见利忘义 -我不知道
- Sellout! - I don't know!
再说你怎么会在这里
And what are you doing here?
我来为诺普招人啊
Well, I'm recruiting for NERP.
我说过我需要一个搞科学的人
I told you I need a science-y person.
你不能自己进来闲逛 你得有入场证
You can't just saunter in here. You have to be approved.
年轻人 我看你不修边幅 你一定很聪明
Oh. Hey, kid. You don't care what you look lik. You must be smart.
你想去一个有很多辣妹的地方上班吗
Want to work at a place that has a lot of hot girls?
别闹了
Stop it!
你还能把情况弄得更糟吗
Could you make this horrible situation any worse?
抵制希洛 赶紧滚吧
Hell no, Helo! It's time you go!
-那不是我干的 -抵制希洛 赶紧滚吧
- I didn't do that. - Hell no, Helo, it's time you go!
我以前从没见过这样成群的书呆
I've never seen nerds swarm like this before!
我们通常不是群聚型的生物
We're not typically a clustering people.
天啊 是阿尔文
Oh, my God. It's Arvin.
糟了 我发邮件告诉他我会来
Oh, no. I emailed him I'd be here.
我等下要尴尬死了
Oh, this is gonna be so awkward for me!
我们最后一次见面时 我伤透了他的心
The last time I saw him, I broke his heart.
你还尴尬
Awkward for you?
这些人都恨我恨到不惜彼此眼神交会了
These people hate me so much, they're making eye contact!
艾丽克丝 你好啊
Alex? Hi!
那些人在干嘛
What's all the com--
海莉
Haley.
阿尔文 你好
Arvin. Hi.
我不知道你会在这
I didn't know you'd be here.
这句话很难说出口
This isn't going to be easy to say.
我结婚了 生了双胞胎
I got married, and I have twins.
是的 我知道
I know. Yes.
那是迪兰节假日新闻邮件的头条
It was the lead story in Dylan's holiday newsletter.
你确定你没偷偷跟进我的现状吗
You sure you haven't been stalking a little?
没有 有新闻邮件就行了
No. No, that's why.
艾丽克斯 这是针对你的吗
Alex, is this directed at you?
是的 没错
Yes. Yes, it is.
他们太刻薄了
And they are so mean!
抵制希洛
Hell no, Helo!
打断一下
Uh, excuse me.
你们都知道我人很好 对吧
Uh, you-you all know I'm a cool guy, right?
你们叫我阿尔文我也不介意
I'm chill with you calling me Arvin.
有一次我们还去室外上课
We had class outside that one time.
大家先暂停一分钟好吗
Will you just give us a minute?
我保证 她会全身心感受到我的愤怒
I assure you, she will feel the full effects of my rage.
-你最近怎么样 -不怎么样
- So, how have you been? - Not so great.
他们不喜欢你的老板吗
They're not fans of your employer?
这太不公平了
Which is so unfair!
我正在做非常前沿的研究
I'm doing very advanced research
很可能会产生深远的影响
that could have far-reaching implications.
是啊 我毫不意外
Yeah. Of course you are.
等一下
One sec.
你晚上怎么睡得着
How do you sleep at night?!
你也和他们一样吗
Okay, so, you, too?
当然不是
No, of course not.
我不是来评判你或你的老板
I am not here to judge you or your boss --
撒旦
Satan!
总之 我只是想路过打个招呼
Anyway, I just thoht I'd drop by and say a quick hello.
海莉 很高兴见到你
Haley, lovely to see you.
别迷恋我了 向前看吧
You have to move on.
艾丽克斯 祝你一切都好 那好
Alex, I wish you nothing but the best. Okay.
好了 大伙 带点感情
Right, guys. Now with feeling.
抵制希洛 赶紧滚吧
Hell no, Helo! It's time you go!
莉莉的话真的让我们很在意
What Lily said really got to us.
或许我们这年纪确实不该要宝宝了
Maybe we are too old to have a new baby.
昨天 我发现自己耳朵上长毛了
Yesterday, I found hairs on my ears
还对着本地新闻大骂
and I yelled at the local news.
我把宋飞说成了"宋灰"
And I called Seinfeld "Steinfeld."
不过话说回来
You know, but on the other hand,
我们这年纪的男人要孩子也挺常见的
there are a lot of men our age having babies.
是的 不过他们都有第二任娇妻和保姆
Yes, but-but they have second wives and nannies --
保姆和娇妻通常是一个人
who are often the same person.
我们需要跟一个
We just needed to talk to a-a parent
上年纪后要宝宝的家长聊聊
that had a baby when they were old.
你们肯定搞错了 因为我生乔时才35
You must be mistaken, because I had Joe when I was 35.
不 我记得 你当时已经...
No, I remember. You had just turned --
她不会承认的
She's not gonna budge.
就跟我们直说吧 有多难
Okay, j-just tell us, how hard is it?
会不会经常没有觉睡
Well, are there nights where you don't sleep
恨不得杀了自己
and you want to kill yourself?
当然会
Of course.
每次抱起放下宝宝时
Are there shooting pains in your back
后背会不会疼得要死
from picking the baby and putting him down?
每次都会
Constantly.
好吧 有转折[臀部]吗
Okay, well, is there a but?
还算能看 跟以前没法比
It's hanging in there, but it's not the same.
我知道你们担心自己太老了
Look, I know that you guys worry that you're too old
反应太慢了 照顾不好宝宝
or too slow to have a baby at this age.
但你猜怎么着
But guess what.
你们可以
You can!
-那是什么鬼 -一个娃娃
- What the hell was that? - A doll.
它本该证明你们准备好了要宝宝
It was supposed to prove that you guys were ready to have a baby,
但假如这是真的宝宝 你们已经摔死它了
but if this was a real one, you would have killed it.
难道不是该怪你乱扔宝宝吗
Well, wouldn't it be your fault for throwing it?
你就饶了我吧 我只是在实验新招
Give me a break. I was trying something.
我正在想办法卖这间房
I'm in the middle of selling a house.
对了 顺带一提 房子很漂亮
Oh, yeah, it's very cute, by the way.
有几间卧室
How many bedrooms is it?
三间带一个小屋
Three and a den.
比我们家卧室多
Oh, that's one more than we have.
米奇尔 这房子真不错
Mitchell, this house, huh?
小卡 我根本不能开始考虑买房
Cam, I can't even begin to think about a house
我们甚至还没决定好
when we haven't even made a decision about whether or not
-要不要领养 -或许这是老天的暗示
- we're going to -- - But maybe it's a sign.
新工作泡汤了 新宝宝要来了
You know, the new job goes away, a baby comes along,
突然间 我们身处这幢迷人的
and all of a sudden, we're standing in a charming
-三卧房子 -还有三间半洗手间
- three-bedroom -- - Three and a half bath.
老天爷 只要我们换回开架护肤霜
Which, holy cow, we could afford if we just switch back
-我们就买得起 -不行
- to grocery store face cream. - No.
这里可是好学区房
And it's in a great school district.
你知道吗 她说得没错
You know what? She's right about that.
他们有全职护士
They have a full-time nurse.
我们只有一盒创可贴和一罐姜汁汽水
We have a Band-Aid jar and a can of ginger ale.
我们手上的难题已经够多了
Okay, we already have too much on our plate.
我们不能买这幢房
We're not buying this house!
地下室还有唱K室
Oh, and in the basement, they have a karaoke room
专为那些想要模仿天后
for people that want to impersonate divas
又不想被老爸看到的人准备
without their fathers seeing them.
我想看看也无妨
Well, I guess it wouldn't hurt to look.
我说不好 我真的看起来像在办公室吗
I don't know, guys. Does it really look like I'm in my office?
《大白鲨》也不是真鲨鱼
Jaws wasn't a real shark,
还是吓得我好几个月不敢坐马桶
but I still wouldn't sit on a toilet seat for months.
这角度怎么样 妈
How's this angle, Mom?
应该可以
Um, uh, fine, I guess.
我的脸颊好痒 我脸上有东西吗
My cheek is itching! Is there something on my face?
你怎么变成外星人了 你这是怎么了
Admiral Ackbar, what the hell happened to you?
肯定是你的破蘑菇害的
I'll bet it was your stupid mushrooms!
我为什么要尝试新事物
Why do I try new things?
我不会换掉我的老爹牛仔裤
I'm sticking to my Brett Favre jeans!
老天 是她 是她
Oh, God! That's her! That's her!
所有人安静
Everybody quiet!
等等 我得上去喂宝宝
Wait, I have to get up there with the babies --
你坐下
Sit!
贝克曼女士
Hi, Ms. Beckman.
非常感谢你给我这次...
Thank you so much for this --
机会
...opportunity.
不客气
You're welcome.
我不是在笑话你
I-I wasn't mocking you.
只不过每次我听到有人打喷嚏
It's just that whenever I hear someone sneeze,
我也必须打喷嚏 让它变成偶数
I have to sneeze, too, so that it's an even number.
这是很正常的
It's-it's perfectly normal.
是的 我完全理解
Oh, no, I completely understand.
几年前 有次从淋浴间出来时
A few years ago, I forgot to tap the towel rod twice
我忘了敲两下毛巾杆
when I got out of the shower,
结果乔治·迈克尔在那天离世了 所以
and we lost George Michael that day, so...
是你害的啊
That was you?
让我为你介绍一下我们的公司
Let me tell you a little bit about our company.
洗耳恭听
I'd love that.
但首先 让我记些笔记
But first, I'd like to take some notes.
往上抬
Tilt up!
这就是我喜欢这个行业的原因
That's what I love about this industry --
从不无聊 保持"尖峰"
never a "Dull" Moment.
没插电
It's not plugged in.
我们对收纳良品的定位是
We like to think of "Organize 'Em"
一家关于健康的公司
as a wellness company --
一家关于正念的公司
A mindfulness company.
你的架子在晃吗
Are your shelv shaking?
是的
Uh...yeah.
是的 好像发生了小地震
Yeah, I think we're having a little earthquake.
不如这样 不如让我
You know what? Why don't I tell you
向你介绍一下自己
a little something about myself?
我认为我是那种
I like to think I'm the kind of person
能看出顾客的消费趋势朝哪倾斜
who can see where the consumer trends are leaning,
做出快速调整
adjust quickly,
然后向反方向倾斜回来的人
and lean back the other direction.
我的天
Oh, my God!
我太喜欢整理了
Do I love organizing!
宝贝 我爱死了
Baby, do I love it!
邓菲女士 你喝酒了吗
M-Ms. Dunphy, have you been drinking?
说谎就行了 她闻不到你一身酒气
Just lie. She can't smell your breath.
不可以 茵素 不可以
No, Poppy, no!
这他妈是在搞什么鬼
What the hell is happening?!
我放弃了
I'm calling it.
抱歉 贝克曼女士 这真是个馊主意
I'm sorry, Ms. Beckman. This was a terrible idea.
我... 好吧
I -- Okay.
我踩破了一格楼梯 我的脚卡住了
I fell through a step, and my leg is stuck.
请听我说 你们是我最想要为之奋斗的公司了
And listen, there's no company I would rather work for.
我不想跟你取消 所以我请我的家人
I didn't want to cancel on you, so I asked my family
把这里布置得像我在办公室里
to make it look like this was my office.
杰·普里契特 柜界先锋 不过估计你早听说过我
Jay Pritchett, closeteer, but you probably know that.
能把他赶离我的听觉范围内吗
Could you just please get him out of my ear shot?
好的好的 没问题
Yeah, yeah, sure.
相信我 我本来很想让你以为
Listen, I wanted you to think that I was a person
我是一个井然有序又成功的人 但我并不是
who had it all together, but I'm not.
现实就是我住在一片混乱之中
The reality is I live in chaos!
这就是为什么我这么爱你们的产品
But that's why I love your products.
每当... 我的孩子们吵架
When -- When my kids are fighting
或者我的孙子女们在哭闹
or -- or the grandkids are crying
又或是我丈夫跳着弹簧高跷做松饼
or my husband is making pancakes on a pogo stick,
我心里知道我可以去到我的办公室
I know that I can go into my office
把各类账单按颜色标记归档
and file bills in a color-coded divider
享受到片刻心灵的宁静
and experience one moment of peace.
我知道你们公司有多需要我
I know I'm what your company needs,
就像我知道我有多需要你们公司
because I know how much I need your company.
我得到工作了
I got the job!
她真是太棒了
I'm so proud of her!
我猜那肯定是我们的幸运阶梯
I guess it's our lucky step.
不用担心 摔的是我
Don't worry. It's just me.
看有多幸运
Oh. See?!
你知道吗 你也可以为我说两句的啊
You know what? You could have defended me!
我该说话吗
Mm. Should I have?
难道你同意他们说的话吗
Are you saying you agree with them?
我觉得他们的口号过于简化了
I found their chant rather simplistic.
如果是我 我估计会说像是...
You know, I would have probably gone with something like...
"希洛动力公司这家跨国企业
"Helo Dynamics is a multinational corporation
只在乎利益而忽视道德"
that prioritizes profits over ethics."
我就知道 你也对我有意见
I knew it. You are judging me.
你这么批判你所有学生吗
Do you judge all of your students like this?
艾丽克斯
Alex...
我其他的学生并没有你的潜力
all my students don't have the potential you do!
你是如此的不凡
You were extraordinary!
你本来应该成为改变世界的人
You were meant to change the world!
而且这并不是我一个人的想法
And it's not just me that thinks it.
迪兰的家庭新闻邮件里也写了
Dylan said so in his newsletter.
饶了我吧
Oh, spare me.
道貌岸然的学者鄙视得意门生
The sanctimonious academic, looking down on the star pupil
就因为她脚踏千金名鞋
because of her thousand-dollar shoes!
那双鞋价值上千吗
Those shoes were a thousand dollars?
哇靠 价格是买鞋附赠一整村子的药物吗
Damn it. Do they come with medicine for a village?
告诉你 我也不想说这话
You know what? I hate to say it,
但我不需要你的认可 因为我喜欢我的工作
but I don't need your approval, because I love what I do.
那真是太遗憾了
Ah. Well, I am sorry to hear that.
-省省吧 -我遗憾是因为我在组织研究团队
- Don't be. - I'm sorry because I am assembling a research team
想要创造无所不能的人工智慧
to create A.I. capable of everything
从发现外太空的系外行星
from discovering exoplanets in deep space
到人体中疾病的生物标记物
to biomarkers of disease in humans.
本来如果有你的加入
And you would've been a superb addition
可以让团队如虎添翼
to an exceptional team.
但拉倒吧
But pbht!
教授
Well, Professor...
你特么可以把这工作
you can take that job...
乖乖交给我
and give it to me.
不过你得付我在原公司的薪水
But I'm going to need you to match my salary!
我不确定我们团队有没有那经费
I'm not sure we have that kind of money.
成交
Deal.
我去看看我还能不能拿回去退钱
I'm gonna go see if I can still return these.
最后来到这美丽的家庭休息区
And finally, back to the beautiful family room.
很棒啊
It's great.
这里很美啊
I mean, it is beautiful.
我仿佛都能看见
I can see you both
你们在这里发生的各种美丽误会了
having a delightful misunderstanding here.
米奇尔 听我说
Okay, now, Mitchell. Hmm?
你知道我这个人很少冲动
You know I'm not usually impulsive --
少来了 你独自去超市买东西时
Please. You never go to the grocery store alone
就没有没带气球回家过
and not come home with a balloon.
但楼上的浴室真的太棒了
But that bathroom upstairs is amazing.
是啊 我... 我也很喜欢我能有独自洗脸台
Yeah, and I -- I do love the idea of me having my own sink.
我们家的打扫阿姨终于可以知道是谁脏乱了
Our housekeeper would finally realize who the real villain is.
行 所以我们应... 应该就下手啊
Okay, so we should -- we should do it!
我们点头吧
Let's do it!
-买下这房子吗 -对啊
- Buy this house? - Yeah.
我们连要不要再领养都还没决定呢
We haven't even made a decision about the baby yet.
另一个中介给我发消息了
Oh. Another broker just sent me a text.
有人6点要出价了
An offer is coming at six o'clock.
这下好了 又一个倒计时
Great. Another ticking clock.
干脆就一边解除一个定时炸弹
Let's also disarm a time bomb
一边在网上用过期的信用卡抢碧昂丝的票吧
while buying Beyonce tickets online with an expired credit card.
你这个例子太扎心 我要喘不过气了
Okay, that one got to me. I'm having hard time breathing.
我感觉我要犯心脏病啦
I feel like I'm gonna have a heart attack!
而这带壁炉的宽敞家庭休息室
And this big family room with the cozy fireplace
正是适合你犯心脏病的完美地点
is the perfect place to have that.
好了好了 歌洛莉亚 别来这套了
Okay, you know what, Gloria? Stop.
我们 我们... 我们需要时间考虑
We -- We -- We need to think.
不不不 我们不需要考虑
No, no, no, we do not need to think.
我们需要的是停手
We need to stop this.
懂吗 在短短的18小时内
Okay, within the span of eighteen hours,
我们就要让生活天翻地覆般改变吗
we're supposed to completely and utterly change our lives?
任何一个改变人生的决定都不该这么定下
No -- No big, life-altering decision should be made that way.
你说得对 好 我们不这么做了
You're right. Here, let's -- Then let's not.
-好 -这样太过火了
- Okay. - It's just way too much.
一件事如果是对的
When things are right,
就不该会有这种纠结感啊
i-it shouldn't be a struggle like this.
你心中会有所感
You just know it.
是啊 我知道
Yeah. I know.
那个小男孩 他会找到很好的家庭的啦
That little boy, he's gonna find an amazing family, right?
-当然会啦 -是的 对
- Of course he is. - Yeah. Yeah.
你知道吗 我已经...
You -- You know what? I already --
感觉负担轻了一些
I already feel a little lighter.
我们也不需要搬家的压力
And we don't need the stress of moving.
-不需要 -你知道为什么吗
- No. - Because you know what?
-因为我爱我们的房子 -我也是
- I love our house. - I do, too.
-它虽然不完美 但我们也不是完人 -我们的确不是
- It is not perfect. But neitare we. - No. We aren't.
你们的车也不行
And neither is your car.
能把你们的破车从车道挪走吗
Can you please remove that thing from the driveway?
我想给这里树立高级生活人设呢
I'm trying to sell a life style here.
是领养机构吗
Is that the adoption ancy?
是的
Yep.
我... 我会告诉他们
I'll -- I'll tell them.
你好
Hello.
对 我跟我丈夫很乐意领养他
Uh, yes, my husband and I would love to adopt him.
起草购买意向书吧
Let's write up an offer.
-小爸 醒醒 -怎么 怎么了
- Dad. Wake up. - Oh, what -- what -- what --
-大爸好像又吃安眠药了 -那他...
- I think Daddy took a sleeping pill again. - Is he...
-是的 -好吧
- Yep. - Okay.
♪ 他教我爱他 ♪
♪ He taught me to love him ♪
♪ 也承诺会爱我 ♪
♪ And promised to love ♪
♪ 视我为世上最珍视之人 ♪
♪ And cherish me over all others above ♪
图森市的观众们 跟我一起唱
Come on, sing it with me, Tucson!
♪ 我可怜的小心肝苦等着 没有任何悲剧可以比拟 ♪
♪ My poor heart is wonderin', no misery can tell -- ♪
米奇尔 有个瑞芭点了鸡翅
Hey, Mitchell. I have a dozen wings for Reba.
是的 好的 谢谢你啦
Yup. Okay, thank you so much.
我们下次见
We'll see you next time.
托尼 我耳返里好像有些杂音
Tony, I'm getting a little feedback in my ear here.
这是托尼·哈蒙德 女士们先生们
Tony Hammond, ladies and gentlemen.